Undercover Bridesmaid is a romance, tv movie film directed by Matthew Diamond.
A bodyguard must go undercover to protect, a tycoon's daughter
from death threats before her big wedding day.
Tanya, played by Brooke Burns.
Daisy, played by Nicole Paggi.
Jake, played by Justin Baldoni.
Mr. Thompson, played by Gregory Harrison.
Betsy, played by Kayla Mae Maloney.
Sally, played by Martha Madison.
Justin Louis Baldoni (born January 24, 1984) is an American actor and director.
He is best known for playing Rafael Solano on the CW telenovela Jane the Virgin (2014–2019) and
for starring in and directing the romantic drama film It Ends with Us (2024).
He has also directed Five Feet Apart (2019) and Clouds (2020).
Baldoni co-founded the production company Wayfarer Studios in 2019.
Through his company he has produced and co-hosted the Man Enough podcast.
He has also published two books on exploring positive masculinity
and overcoming societal expectations of being a man.
He is also currently involved in litigation after Blake Lively, who co-starred
with him in It Ends with Us, accused him of sexual harassment.
The tone is emotional.